airstream.com 2017-01-31

# Privacy Policy, Travel Trailers, Touring Coaches | Airstream

**AIRSTREAM, INC. WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY**

We recognize the importance of protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to information Airstream, Inc. obtains from and about individuals interacting with Airstream, Inc. via the website(s) it operates (the “Website”). This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Website or otherwise.

**TYPES OF INFORMATION AIRSTREAM, INC. MAY COLLECT OR TRACK**

**Personal Information.** Personal information is information, which can be used to specifically identify you. We collect personal information when you submit it to us. For example, we collect personal information when you communicate with us, when you submit content to the Website, when you indicate an interest in our products, and when you purchase or register our products. We may also lawfully obtain information from other companies within the Thor Industries, Inc. corporate family and from third party sources, such as independent dealers, Airstream, Inc. licensees, Airstream, Inc.’s vendors, and other companies which provide lists of potential customers.

The personal information collected by Airstream, Inc. may include:

  1. Your name, address, e-mail address, social media addresses, telephone number and other contact information;
  2. Your Social Security Number;
  3. Your billing information, including your credit card number, cardholder name, expiration date, and billing address;
  4. Information concerning AIRSTREAM products you have purchased, including sales records, Vehicle Identification Numbers, make, model, selling dealer, service history and information obtained during product registration);
  5. Information concerning AIRSTREAM products in which you may be interested in purchasing or have purchased in the past;
  6. Content you submit to Airstream, Inc. via any AIRSTREAM-related Website, solicitation, promotion, or contest, including messages, essays, statements, photographs and videos; and
  7. Information accessed from social media providers, if you make use of any Website social media features, in accordance with the social media providers’ policies.

**Other Non-Personal Information.** We may also gather non-personal information that does not personally identify you. This information may include general demographic information, automatically-collected session information (such as your browser and information collected by cookies and related technologies), and compiled data.

Like many other commercial websites, our Website uses “cookies” and web server log files to collect information about how our Website is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Website, and the websites visited just before and just after our Website.

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit our Website, our site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Any website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Website will not function as effectively when viewed by the users. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive.

We also work with third-parties to provide us with analyses of the usage and browsing patterns of visitors to our Website by tracking non-personally identifiable information about our visitors and customers. We also use similar technology to serve online advertising promoting products which our visitors and customers may be interested. These third parties include Google Analytics and Facebook. These services are cookie-based and do not collect personal information. Each third party is subject to its own privacy policy.

Through our Website, we may also collect non-personal information about the device you use to access the Website, your IP addresses, geo-location information, and unique device identifiers. While we may log your IP address for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes, we do not use your IP address to track your session, nor do we associate your IP address to anything personally identifiable.

**“DO NOT TRACK” SIGNALS**

Airstream, Inc.’s Website honors “do not track” signals.

**CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT**

Our Website does not track your personal information over time or track personally-identifiable browsing history over other sites. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not permit third parties to gather your personally identifiable information over time and/or across different websites when using our Website. Our Website may, however, either directly or through a third party service provider, track non-personal data or browsing history over time through the use of an anonymous unique identifier.

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY DISCLOSURES**

California residents may request Airstream to provide information concerning the manner in which Airstream shares certain categories of your personal information with third parties for direct marketing activities by third parties. The information may be presented in a standardized format not specific to you individually. The information will include: (1) the categories of information Airstream disclosed to third parties during the preceding calendar year for the purpose of direct marketing by the third party; and (2) the names and addresses of third parties to which Airstream provided such information, or, if the nature of the business of a third party cannot be discerned from the name, then examples of the products or services marketed. California residents may request this information by calling Airstream at 937-596-6111.

**HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

Airstream, Inc. uses your information generally to communicate with you, to provide you information concerning products or services you may request, to provide independent dealers with information concerning your potential interest in Airstream, Inc. products, to manage your account; to register products your have purchased; to administer warranty and service claims; to measure interest in and improve Airstream, Inc.’s products; to solicit information from you; and to enable use of the Website and associated online services.

We may share your information with third parties who provide services or functions on behalf of Airstream (such as billing, e-commerce, credit card processing, business analytics, marketing and promotional services, customer research, surveys, and fraud detection and prevention). Note that sensitive billing information is used only for the purposes of fulfilling transactions within the Website and/or through vendors providing online commerce services to Airstream, Inc.

We also use third party services (such as Google Analytics and Facebook) which assist us in analyzing the use of our Website and which provide advertising and marketing services. These services are cookie-based and do not collect or share personal information.

We may share your personal information with independent dealers. This may include forwarding referrals to dealers to advise them of your potential interest in an AIRSTREAM product. This may also include information about products you have purchased, including registration information and information relating to warranty and/or service issues.

We may provide information to marketing partners to help identify products and offers which may be of interest to you. This may include the sharing of non-personally identifiable information (such as aggregated data or data gathered by Internet “cookies”) or it may include personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email address and telephone number) for use in direct marketing efforts.

Airstream, Inc. may also share your information with third-party business partners with whom we jointly offer products, with whom we are engaging in cross-promotional efforts, whose products are offered on our Website, or who offer products which we believe would be of interest to our users.

We may disclose information when legally required to do so (for example, in response to a court order or subpoena). We may also disclose information when in good faith we believe disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, or to protect the safety of our users or the Public.

We may share your information with other companies within the Thor Industries, Inc. corporate family.

When you access certain social media features through our Website, you will be sharing information with that social media provider. The information you provide to that social media provider will be governed by their privacy policy, not ours.

We may also disclose information during a corporate transaction, such as a merger or a sale of the business or an asset of the business.

**“OPTING OUT” AND CORRECTING YOUR INFORMATION**

You may choose to opt out of receiving email communications from Airstream, Inc. at any time by sending an e-mail request to: [marketing@airstream.com](mailto:marketing@airstream.com). Please include “Opt Out Request” in your subject line.

You may also request that Airstream, Inc. does not share your personal information with third parties for the purposes of marketing or advertising purposes, including direct marketing. You may choose to opt out of the sharing of personal information by Airstream, Inc. at any time by submitting an email with “Opt Out Request” in the subject line to: Marketing@airstream.com or by sending a written request to:

Airstream C/O Marketing

P.O. Box 629

Jackson Center, OH 45334

While you may choose to opt out of the sharing of your personal information for marketing purposes, we reserve the right to use your personal information for the other purposes set forth above (for example, for billing or for warranty and service issues).

We encourage you to contact Airstream, Inc. with any questions you may have regarding this Privacy Statement or Airstream, Inc.’s privacy practices. You may also contact us if you wish to correct any information which Airstream, Inc. may have concerning you (for example, name, address, e-mail address or telephone number).

Please send your questions or requests for correction to: Marketing@airstream.com or

Airstream C/O Marketing

P.O. Box 629

Jackson Center, OH 45334

**PROTECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION**

While no website or computer system is guaranteed to be secure, Airstream, Inc. has adopted appropriate administrative, technical and physical procedures to protect the personal information you provide to us against unauthorized access. In the unlikely event of a data breach, Airstream, Inc. will comply with applicable notice requirements.

**AIRSTREAM INDEPENDENT DEALERS**

Airstream, Inc. markets and sells recreational vehicles through independent dealers. Airstream, Inc. and dealers may share information concerning your personal identifying information, interests, and product registrations. Please know that dealers are separate legal entities, and dealers are not governed by this Privacy Policy. While Airstream, Inc. encourages its dealers to comply with applicable laws, Airstream, Inc. is not responsible for dealers’ compliance with their privacy policies or applicable law. Please contact your dealer directly if you have questions about your dealer’s privacy policy, including opting out of marketing communications.

**EXTERNAL LINKS**

The Website may contain links to third party websites, including those operated by business which provide e-commerce services to Airstream, Inc. Those third party websites are not bound by this Privacy Policy. Please review the terms and conditions and policies associated with those third party websites for further information.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

The Website is intended for use by persons over the age of 18. We do not knowingly target or collect personal information from any person under the age of 18.

**USING THE WEBSITE FROM OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

Airstream, Inc. maintains this website in the State of Ohio in the United States of America, and this Website is intended for viewing within the United States only. These Terms of Service are governed by and are to be construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Ohio. Airstream, Inc. does not represent or warrant that this Website complies with the laws of any other jurisdiction. The data protection and privacy laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those of other countries. If you access this Website from outside of the United States, you remain responsible for compliance with any applicable laws.

**UPDATES AND REVISIONS**

Airstream, Inc. reserves the right to update or change any terms of this Privacy Policy without prior notice by posting changes or updates to this webpage.

**Effective date: April 7, 2015**

**Last modified: April 7, 2015**
